本字幕由 YYeTs人人影视 原创翻译制作
仅供学习 禁止用于任何商业盈利行为
更多字幕下载 请登陆 www.YYeTs.com
■
圣  城  风  云
『第一季  第八集』
翻译  Jasmine雪
翻译  LyraL
翻译  ala365
翻译  小熊嘟嘟
翻译  小易
时间轴  veryink
后期  渔夫
特效  WiLL
总监制  苏小黛
你到底有何企图
What do you want with me?
嘘  孩子
Shush, child.
好好休息
Rest now.
你很安全
You're safe.
安全
Safe?
早安
Good morning.
不行  太做作了
No, that's too much.
早安
Good morning.
这还行
Yeah.
请进
Yes?
早安
Good morning.
谢谢你  薇薇安
Thank you, Vivian.
要我去叫醒摩根吗
Shall I wake Morgan?
坐下
Sit down.
你的忠心究竟有几分
How absolute is your loyalty?
对谁
To whom?
对摩根
To Morgan.
对这座城堡内所有的人
And to everyone within these walls.
我大半辈子都效命于此
I've served here most of my life.
摩根命令你毫无质疑的接受
Morgan requests that you accept my instructions
我的指令
without question.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
卡米洛特
At Camelot.
我们的国家正日趋混乱
The land is falling towards disarray.
她和她弟弟有些问题需要解决
There are matters she must resolve with her brother.
于此同时
In the meantime,
我需要个信得过的人
I need someone I can trust.
你之前
What you said...
说的
...before.
你说的没错  我...
You were right. I...
应该更开放一点
...could be more open.
我  缺乏练习
I'm... out of practice.
你随时可以找我练习
You can always practice with me.
也许会的
Maybe I will.
摩根在哪
Where's Morgan?
她去哪儿了
Where is she?
求你  传个话
Please. Tell someone.
找个人来
Get someone.
求你  帮帮我
Please, help me.
回来  求你了
Come back. Please!
求求你
Please!
回来啊
Come back!
求你回来
Please come back!
求求你  回来
Please! Come back!
此事只有你知我知
You and I are the only ones to know about this.
你宣誓过效忠于摩根
You swore that your loyalty to Morgan was absolute.
现在是证明你的忠心的时候了
Now prove it.
早安  夫人
My lady. Good morning.
-早安  -里昂提斯
- Good morning. - Leontes.
伊格兰夫人
Lady Igraine.
早安
Good morning.
夫人
Milady.
打扰了  夫人
Excuse me, milady,
这些要放哪里
where would you like these?
放在常放的地方就行了
Uh, the usual place will be fine.
-早安  -早安
- Good morning. - Good morning.
早安  夫人
Good morning, milady.
-早安  -我把你的披肩放回去了
- Good morning. - Oh, I put your shawl back.
我看到了  谢谢你
I saw. Thank you.
夫人
Madame.
早安
Good morning.
当然  我会通知手下  殿下
Yes, of course. I'll tell the men, Your Highness.
-早安  -早安  亚瑟
- Good morning. - Good morning, Arthur.
我想感谢你  感谢你在遇袭那晚
I never thanked you for your support
对我的支持
the other night during the attack.
你的支持好比雪中送碳
It was exactly what I needed.
应该的
Of course.
早安  桂妮维尔
Good morning, Guinevere.
这些事不用你来做的
You don't have to do that.
-我喜欢自己动手  -要帮忙吗
- I like doing it. - Can I help?
谢谢
Thank you.
在彭德拉根
What I said...
我所说的话
...at Pendragon...
我明白的
I know.
我不该说出来的
I shouldn't have said it.
但我是真心的
But I did mean it.
你吻了我
You kissed me.
你父亲死后  我们回程的路上
On our journey back, after your father's death.
我只是出于悲伤
It was grief.
那一刻之前  我已埋葬了所有的情愫
I buried everything until that moment.
我很抱歉
I'm sorry.
但你我之间绝无可能
But it will never happen.
我明白
I know.
很抱歉告诉你我的感受
I'm sorry for telling you.
我很欣慰你说了
I'm glad you did.
伊格兰  伊格兰
Igraine? Igraine!
-你去哪儿了  -怎么了
- Where have you been? - What do you mean?
我一直在等你
I've been waiting.
是啊  我太无礼了  真对不起
Of course. How rude of me! I'm sorry.
我...我之前有点事
I... had an errand to run.
卡米洛特正处于险境  只有你能救我们
Camelot's in danger. Only you can save us,
瑞德伍德阁下  我勇敢的真正的骑士
Sir Redwald, my brave and true knight.
别怕  伊格兰夫人
Fear not, my Lady Igraine,
我是您的护卫  卡米洛特会得救的
for I am your champion and Camelot will be saved.
那是我  他也是个孤儿
That's supposed to be me. He's an orphan, too.
-当然  -我降服了我们敌方
- Of course. - I faced down our enemy's
最厉害的战士  并战胜了他  是为了你
toughest warrior, and bested him. For you.
都是为了你
All for you.
好
Um. OK. Oh...
好吧
Um... OK...
你真是个勇敢的护卫  我要怎么回报你
Uh, you are a truly brave champion. How can I ever repay you?
现在我们该结婚  并永远在一起了
Now we shall be married and live together forever.
这就是结尾了
That's the end, really.
我喜欢结局圆满的故事
Well, I love a story with a happy ending.
这个结局非常完美
And that one is very happy.
等我长大
When I get older,
我们就真结婚  你就能真的能做我的王后了
we'll really marry, and you can be my queen for real.
我想  我对你来说可能太老了
I think that, um, I might be a little too old for you.
我不介意  我很成熟
I don't mind. I'm very grown up.
那好的
Well, that's all right, then.
你孤独吗
Are you lonely?
你  你怎么会这么问
Why... why would you ask that?
你的眼睛今天看起来好哀伤
Your eyes look so sad today.
我有你这样的朋友
How could I be lonely
怎么会觉得孤独呢
when I have a friend like you?
求你
Please.
告诉我为何困我于此
Tell me why I'm here.
当初摩根回来的时候
When Morgan returned here,
她父亲将她拒之门外
when her father rejected her,
你为何不帮她说话
why didn't you speak for her?
你为何不说服他再给她一次机会
Why didn't you convince him to give her another chance?
就是为了这个吗
Is that what this is?
为了当日之事  惩罚我
Punishment... for that day?
我们都要吃自己所种的苦果
We are all the victims of our own actions.
是你自己的抉择让你落到如此地步
It is your own decisions that have brought you here.
如果你愿告解
Perhaps if you were to confess,
也许会找到慰藉
you would find solace.
告解什么
Confess what?
那就要你自己决定了
That is for you to decide.
但不告解是不能得到救赎的
But there can be no salvation without it.
等他们找到我
When they find me,
等我获救
when I'm rescued,
需要哀求宽恕的人就是你了
you will be the one that needs forgiveness.
我的灵魂是没有瑕疵的
My soul is without stain.
是吗
Really?
我们中只有一个
Only one of us
做了婊子  生了杂种
whored herself and sired a bastard.
卫兵  卫兵
Guards! Guards!
卫兵
Guards!
-把她拽开  -我要杀了她
- Get her off me! - I will kill her!
你不会的  别逼我伤害你
No you won't. Don't make me cut you.
你有过机会了  但你不却下不了手
You had your chance, but you couldn't take it.
守在门口  把门锁好
Stay outside the room. Keep the door locked.
别跟她说话
Do not talk to her.
别听她说话  也别迁就她任何要求
Do not listen to her. Do not accede to any of her requests.
她要是再找麻烦
Should she cause further trouble,
你可以酌情使用武力
you may use force, at your discretion.
-有什么问题吗  -没有
- Do you have any questions? - No.
很好
Good.
走吧  薇薇安
Come along, Vivian.
我知道你有疑虑  孩子
I know you have your doubts, child.
但等摩根处理完卡米洛特中心的
But Morgan will return when she has dealt
黑暗势力  她就会回来的
with the darkness at the heart of Camelot.
什么黑暗势力  她在做什么
What darkness? What is she doing?
要有耐心  孩子
Have patience, child.
一切都会按计划实现的
Everything will fall into place.
-这就来了  -我说真的
- Here they come. - I'm telling you,
她真的喜欢我
she really liked me.
-她说她会来看我  -你说谁啊
- She said she'd come and visit! - And who is this?
彭德拉根那晚的一位舞娘
One of the dancers from the other night at Pendragon.
-布拉提斯恋爱了  -我没有
- Brastias is in love. - I'm not in love!
-但是  我们心心相印啊  -可不是么
- But... we had a connection. - Oh, we know.
我们在院子里都听到了
We could hear it out in the courtyard.
谁换个话题
Somebody change the subject.
告诉他们我们刚刚在讨论的事
Tell them what we were discussing.
六个人想会比两个人好
Six minds are better than 2.
是五个人再加上布拉提斯
Well, 5 minds plus Brastias.
-想什么  -想我们努力的方向
- On what? - On what we're working towards.
我们想有所成就  功绩就要永世长存
If we're going to achieve anything, it has to live long after us.
我们不仅要领导人民
It's not enough that we lead.
还要改变人们的观念
We have to change how people think.
-那要怎么做  -要通过人民
- How are we going to do that? - It has to be through the people.
人民不会更迭变化  他们向他们的
They're the constant, what they pass on
孩子传授如何生活的理念
to their children about how to live.
伙计们  我们是来打猎还是来聊天了
Lads, with respect, are we talking, or are we hunting?
记着  一次做一件
Remember, one thing at a time.
布拉提斯的舞娘也这么抱怨来着
That was Brastias's dancer's complaint, as well.
布拉提斯  高文  欧菲尔斯
Brastias, Gawain, Ulfius,
你们走山脊  我们在下面伏着
you take the ridge line. We'll stay down low.
野鸡  野兔  野猪  能找着的都行
Pheasant, hare, boar, whatever you can find.
猎物最多者赢
Greatest number wins.
又发号施令了  里昂提斯
Taking charge again, Leontes?
是团队合作  高文
Working as a unit, Gawain.
你们不会比我们打的多的  你们从没
You're not going to get more than us! You've never managed
比我们打的多过  无意冒犯  殿下
more than us. With respect, Your Highness.
我们日落时再回到这里相见  带着猎物
We'll meet back here at sundown, with our catch.
-胜败自见分晓  -好啊
- We'll see who's better. - Fair enough.
我有了很多的  想法
I had more... thoughts.
很好
I like it.
-嗯  -是啊
- Hm! - Yes.
那么
So,
-你打算怎么做  -你指什么
- what are you going to do? - About what?
摩根
Morgan.
你怎么知道我在想那个
How do you know that's what I'm thinking about?
我可以不去管她的阴谋诡计
I could just leave her to her tricks
就像前几天晚上那样
like the other night.
你怎么知道那是诡计
How do you know it was a trick?
她在玩弄我们  监视我们
She was toying with us, watching us,
看我们如何应对
seeing how we'd react.
她为何要那么做
Why would she do that?
为了王位
The crown.
不管她嘴上怎么说  她仍觊觎着王位
Whatever she says, she still wants it.
她永远不会原谅我们为亚瑟所做一切
She'll never forgive either of us for Arthur.
你是否觉得
Do you think that
你对她可能有点过于执着了
maybe you're getting a little obsessed with her?
甚至...
Or...
...你可能是被她迷上了
...perhaps you're attracted to her?
好吧  被你看穿了
There we go. You've seen right through me.
我迷上她了
I'm besotted with her.
如果是尤瑟就会说  带上人过去
Uther would have said go in there with our men,
把她赶走
have her removed.
或处决掉
Or executed.
基于什么理由呢
On what grounds?
我们不需要理由
Ah, we wouldn't need grounds.
可以弄成意外
Accidents happen.
一有机会就干掉你的敌人
Remove your enemies at the first opportunity.
那是他的处世之道
That was his approach.
也许你比他聪明
Then maybe you're wiser than him.
也许更软弱
Or weaker.
如果她连自己的父亲都可以杀
If she can kill her own father,
就什么都做得出来
she's capable of anything.
我不明白你怎么会做出这种结论
I don't see why that's true.
他是你丈夫
He was your husband.
是啊  但他也有过失
Yes, and I wasn't blind to his faults.
她从修道院回来之时
When she came back from the nunnery,
尤瑟打了她
Uther beat her
就当着我的面
in front of me.
接着羞辱了她
And then he humiliated her.
拒绝了她
Rejected her.
永远拒绝了她
Forever.
所以她才弑父
So, therefore, patricide.
解决家庭纠纷的老套路
The age-old solution to a family dispute.
我可不是那个意思
That's not what I'm saying.
我希望她在这里
I wish she were here.
什么意思
What do you mean?
我希望她可以来看看
I wish she could see
并理解我们的所作所为
and understand what we're trying to do.
就像你这样
Like you have.
不过  你比她强多了
But then, you're twice the woman she is.
是吗
Is that right?
不过很遗憾  我想错了
It's a shame, though. I got it wrong.
我以为  她一旦看到...
I thought, once she saw...
...她就会投奔我们
...she'd come to us.
她属于这里
This is where she belongs.
但她作出了选择
But she made her choices,
错误的选择
and they're the wrong ones.
你带食物来了吗
Did you bring the food?
什么食物
Food?
我们不是准备去给他惊喜吗
Aren't we going to surprise him?
想起来了
Oh! Of course.
我忘了
I forgot.
没关系
Never mind.
我去弄点  稍后再来找你
I'll get it, and then I'll come and find you.
自从做了国王  我很久没打猎了
It's been too long since I've done this.
以前凯和我经常一起狩猎
Kay and I used to do it all the time.
这是我和父亲一起干过的
It's one of the first things
印象最深的事之一
I remember doing with my father.
他以前常带我去抓野猪
He used to take me out hunting for boar.
你抓到过吗
Did you catch it?
他把动物血涂在我身上
He blooded me from the animal.
他告诉我  我成为男人了
He told me I'd now become a man.
当时我才五岁
I was 5 at the time.
他找到窝了
I think he's in place.
两箭全中
Both shots hit the target.
我们合作很默契啊
We make a good team.
很不错
Huh? Not bad.
-太好了  -射得漂亮
- Not bad at all. - Good shot.
谢谢
Thank you.
-这是我的战果  -该你了
- Ah, my kill. - Time for yours.
太棒了
Very nice.
你准备好了吗
Are you ready?
稍等
Just a moment.
你真该看看她的眼睛  欧菲尔斯
You should've seen her eyes, Ulfius.
当时你睡着了  他放弃了
As you slept, and he abstained,
剩下我和女神在云雨
I communed with a goddess.
到底是谁在打猎时唠唠叨叨啊
Now who's talking when they should be hunting?
你批评的对  但她太迷人了
You're right, but she was gorgeous.
里昂提斯为他和亚瑟
Of course, Leontes took the best ground
抢占最好的地盘
for the king and himself.
在这里我们肯定没什么收获
We'll not snare much up here.
如果我们多聆听
Well, maybe if we work more with our ears,
少废话
instead of our mouths,
也许会有更好的机会
we might stand a better chance.
等等  看
Wait. Look!
乖乖
You beauty.
我不明白  出什么事了
I don't understand. Is everything all right?
瑞德雷德  我们得谈一谈
Redwald, we need to talk.
我做错什么了吗
Did I do something wrong?
我知道你没生日
I understand you don't have a birthday.
没有
No.
那不太好
That's not good.
每个人都该有生日
Everyone should have a birthday.
抱歉
I'm sorry.
伊格兰和我讨论了这个问题
Igraine and I have been discussing it,
我们觉得唯一的解决办法就是...
and we feel the only solution is...
...就把今天当作你的生日
...today must be your birthday.
这些...是你的礼物
And these... are your gifts.
现在你正式成为国王的战士了
Now you're officially the king's man.
差点忘了...
Oh, I almost forgot...
真漂亮
They're beautiful.
这是国王
The king,
这是他的勇士  他的母亲
his champion, his mother.
这是你
It's you.
是的
Yes.
给我讲故事吧
Tell me the story.
还要听
Again?
你确定吗
You sure?
这故事很好听
It's a good story.
是很好听
It is a good story.
从前  有个地方
Once, in a land
那里终年阳光明媚
where the sun shone all year,
伫立着一个城堡叫卡米洛特
stood a place called Camelot,
那里有位年轻的国王
where a boy king
还有他高贵的勇士和战士们
and his noble champion and their warriors
他们为了人民的自由而战
fought for the freedom of their people.
在那里
And in that place,
每个孤儿都有庇护之所
every orphan was offered shelter.
有一个男孩叫...  他叫什么来着
And a boy named... What was his name?
瑞德伍德
Redwald!
对  叫瑞德伍德
Yes, Redwald.
他找到了一户人家   长大后成为了
Found a family, and grew up to become
国王最出色  最厉害的战士
the king's finest and most fearsome warrior.
看到吗
You see,
人人都有希望
no one was ever without hope,
无论他们是谁
no matter who they were.
卡米洛特能接纳任何人
Within Camelot was a place for everyone.
我知道你能听见我说话
I know that you can hear me.
他们说过为何要把我关在这里吗
Have they told you why I'm in here?
我当时正要离开城堡
I was leaving the castle,
她们把我劫持到这里
and they abducted me and held me here.
而你却助纣为虐
And now you're helping them.
我是国王的母亲
I am the king's mother!
亚瑟若知道你们如此对我
Do you understand what will happen
定不会轻饶你们
when he finds out what's been done to me?
省省吧
Save your energy.
比比吧
Come on!
你们不可能打这么多
There's no way you shot that!
好像咱们这边赢了
Looks like we're the victors, boys.
才不是呢  你们只是走运而已
No, no, you got lucky, that's all!
陛下  您就继续自欺欺人吧
Keep telling yourself that, Your Highness.
凯  这块给你
Oh, Kay, this is for you.
好的
All right.
好了  我们不能仅限于行军打仗
All right, so we need to be more than warriors.
我们要团结所有村庄
We need to bring every village into the fold,
令他们有权参与政事
somehow give them a say in how they wish to be governed.
您是说仿效罗马的议院制
You're talking about a senate, like the Romans had.
我不知道  应该是吧
I don't know. I suppose.
这样如何  让每个村庄或地区选举一位勇士
What if each village or area sent us a champion--
-派来这里  -作为各方代表
- someone they chose themselves? - To represent their cause.
对  当然他们还是忠诚于你
Yes, but ultimately they'd be loyal to you.
勇士委员会  我喜欢
A council of champions. I like it.
还得比你们三个会打猎才行
So long as they're better hunters than you three.
这家伙还有点脑子
The man has a point.
我不困
I'm not tired.
男孩们
Boys...
都要多休息
...need their sleep.
勇士要有好身体才行
Champions need their strength.
今天是最高兴的一天   谢谢你们
Today was the best day. Thank you.
好好睡
You sleep well.
伊格兰  我爱你
I love you, Igraine.
我知道
Yes.
你很会哄他
You're good with him.
你有孩子吗
Do you have children?
或者以前有过
Or did you? Before?
什么以前
Before what?
来此地以前
Before this.
你可以去任何地方  做任何事
You could be anywhere. Do anything.
为何偏要来这里
Why here?
为何要做这些
Why this?
我浪迹天涯多年  有时想要安顿下来
I ran for a long time. Sometimes you have to stop.
跟没回答一样
That's not even half an answer.
哪里
No.
还不承认  你真是恼人
No. You're infuriating!
-我  -当然
- Me? - Yes.
那就随便问我一个问题
Well, so ask me anything. One question.
我保证知无不言
I promise to answer.
你对我有何看法
What do you think about me?
为何一定要问呢
Why do you always have to ask?
你难道不知道吗
Can't you see?
不知道
No.
我对你了解太少
There's so much about you I don't know.
知道这些很重要吗
And why is knowing so important?
如果不能互相了解
How can we trust each other,
何谈相互信任
if we don't know the truth of who we are?
你真要执着于此吗
Are you that fixed?
你确信你就是真实的自己吗
So certain of who you are?
可能
Maybe.
但你怎知明天不会改变
But how do you know you won't change tomorrow?
我知道会变
Hmm, I'm sure I will.
但我知道自己今晚是谁
But I know who I am tonight.
那么  是谁呢
And who is that?
想和你一夜缠绵的人
Someone who wants you.
你在害怕什么
What are you so scared of?
失控
Losing control.
晚安
Good night.
不
No!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
瑞德伍德...
Oh. Redwald...
-刚才你的脸变了  -不  没有
- Your face changed. - No, no. No...
不  你不舒服
No. You're not well.
瑞德伍德...
Redwald...
你爱我吗
Do you love me?
你是我的护卫吗  那这件事...
Are you my champion? Then this...
是咱们之间的小秘密  明白吗
...has to be our little secret. Do you understand?
可是你不舒服
You're not well.
-我没事   -我去找梅林
- I'm fine! - I'm gonna get Merlin!
不要  不要
No! No!
不
No!
不  不
No! No!
为什么不杀了它
Why didn't you kill it?
因为它不仅仅是一只狼
'Cause it was more than a wolf.
-什么意思  -他就是没胆儿而已
- What do you mean? - He means he lost his nerve.
早知如此
Might've known.
欧菲尔斯
Ulfius.
真的离你很近吗
It was close enough to touch?
为何觉得那狼是故意放了你
Why do you think it spared you?
因为它对我另有所图
Because it has another purpose for me.
我发现时已经这样了
I found him like this.
可能这孩子梦游
Maybe he was sleepwalking.
不知不觉绊倒了
Tripped and fell and knew nothing about it.
他的衣服被撕破了
His clothes were torn.
也许是掉下来的时候挂到台子上了
Maybe they ripped on the boards as he fell.
不
No.
肯定有人知道真相
Someone knows what happened.
你没事吧
Are you all right?
没事
Fine.
你如此疼爱他
You cared for him.
我几乎不认识他  何来疼爱
I barely knew him. How could I care for him?
梅林  在我面前  你无需掩饰
Merlin, you don't have to pretend with me.
最有趣的是...
...most amusing...
有人受伤了  快来人
Someone's hurt! Quickly, we need some help!
这种伤天害理的人应该被烧死
Whoever did this deserves to burn.
快来人帮忙  有人受伤了
We need some help here! Someone's hurt!
如果我查出是谁干的
And when I find out who it is,
我会亲自施以火刑
I'll light the pyre myself.
这种禽兽不如的人罪该万死
There's no redemption for a person like this.
那修女走了吗
Has the nun gone?
别跟我说话
Don't speak to me.
你是道纳尔对吗
It is Donal, isn't it?
我记得你父亲曾是这里的铁匠
I remember that your father used to be the blacksmith here.
我们也记得你
And we remember you.
你就是那个目中无人的王后
The stuck-up queen with no time for anyone.
如果真是如此...
Well, if that is true...
我怎会知道你的名字
...how would I know your name?
你觉得摩根知道你的名字吗
Do you think that Morgan knows your name?
道纳尔  求求你
Donal... please.
听我说  片刻就好
Just listen to me, just for a moment.
他们为什么要困住国王的母亲
Why would they lock up the king's mother?
为什么
Why?
你知道这会引起很多麻烦的
You know there'll be trouble about this.
国王会来找我
The king will come for me.
一定会有人救我的  等出去了
I will get out of here, and when I do,
我定会报答你  救救我
there will be a reckoning. Help me.
我发誓会让国王恕你无罪
And I swear I will make sure that the king spares you.
就这么点
That's it?
你就只能答应这点儿
That's all you're offering?
将来可能恕我无罪
Possible future clemency?
道纳尔  告诉我你想要什么
Well, Donal, tell me what you want.
你有什么要求
Tell me what it would take.
尽管说
Name it.
告诉我  我能给你什么
Tell me what I can give you.
可怜的孩子
Poor boy.
自幼便没了母亲  随后...
Brought up without a mother, and then...
父亲又在攻打洛特的时候战死
...loses his father in a battle against Lot.
终于在这里有了家
He found a home here.
对啊  你也是
Yes, just like you.
大家都是如此
Like all of us.
而这也正是亚瑟的志向所在
That's what Arthur's building here.
跟我说实话
Tell me the truth.
你和亚瑟之间到底发生了什么
What happened between you and Arthur?
我不明白你所指何事
I don't know what you're talking about.
就在你婚礼之前  对吗
It was before your wedding day, wasn't it?
伊格兰
Igraine.
那天我看见他和你脸色异常
I saw his face, and yours that day.
肯定有事发生
Something had happened.
你为何现在要问我这些
Why are you asking me this now?
瑞德伍德就这样惨遭毒手
Look at what happened to Redwald.
死亡仿佛阴魂不散
See how death stalks us in life.
所以我们时刻都要
How we must live
随心而活
every moment for what we wish.
我知道
I know what it is
生活在悔恨中的滋味
to live with regret,
数年之后猛然惊醒
to wake up years later,
悔不当初
wishing that I'd done things differently.
我不知道你在说什么
I don't know what you're talking about.
说谎的眼睛  一看便知
I know a liar's eyes when I see them.
我能看出你和亚瑟说话时的眼神
I see the way you talk to Arthur,
你的姿势
the way you stand,
还有你身体里的欲望
the longing in your bodies.
你应该觉得幸运
You're lucky that
里昂提斯已经被爱蒙蔽了双眼
Leontes is too blinded by love to see.
这事折磨得你几近崩溃对吗
It's destroying you, isn't it?
说给我听听
Share it.
那是在我婚礼当天
It was my wedding day.
我也有过犹豫
I had doubts.
但最后还是在一起了
We were together.
-请不要告诉里昂提斯  -当然不会
- Please don't tell Leontes. - Of course not.
你是个善良忠贞的女人
You are a good and faithful woman.
你做出了正确的决定
And you made the right decision.
发誓你会放了我
Swear you'll release me.
得先给甜头才行
Payment first.
现在谁才是你的王
Who's your king now?
亚瑟
Arthur!
你没事吧
Are you all right?
会好的
I will be.
上帝为何要将瑞德伍德从我们身边带走
Why would God want to take Redwald from us?
上帝有时只会静默不语
He doesn't always give answers.
我只能安慰自己
All I can think is
他想将瑞德伍德留在身边
that he wished Redwald to be by his side.
里昂提斯  你是个好人
You are a good man, Leontes.
桂妮薇尔能嫁给你是她的福气
Guinevere is lucky to have you.
你有这样的
A man with a...
大丈夫气度  一定能原谅
...big enough heart to forgive.
原谅什么
What do I have to forgive?
亚瑟和桂妮薇尔
Arthur and Guinevere.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
对不起
Oh! Oh, dear, I'm sorry.
我以为你知道...
I... I didn't realize that you didn't--
等等  知道...知道什么
No, no, you didn't... you didn't realize what?
不说了不说了  对不起
No, no, please, sorry.
是我让大家难堪了
I've embarrassed us both.
告诉我你什么意思
Tell me what you meant.
我以为他们告诉你了
Well, I thought they told you.
他们在你们结婚那天的事
What happened between them on your wedding day.
你什么意思
What are you talking about?
天啊
Oh, God.
我...很抱歉
Oh, I... I'm so sorry!
-伊格兰  伊格兰  -对不起
- Igraine. Igraine. - I'm sorry.
你怎么来了
What are you doing in here?
我今晚不想独自一人
I don't want to be alone tonight.
可是只要我触到
But when I touch,
任何接触
any contact,
我都能看见
I see...
很多东西
...too much.
我能看见人们的本来面目
I see who people really are.
你什么意思
What do you mean?
他们...
Visions...
过去和未来的幻象
...of their past or future.
他们的所有
Whatever their...
伤痛
...traumas are.
以及秘密
Their secrets.
我不怕
I don't mind.
怎么了
What's the matter?
没什么
Nothing.
因为我没什么见不得人的
Because I have nothing to hide.
早上好
Good morning.